{
    "id": "40468bd034df48a7866f82c6e53b5c49",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercie",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They broke ......................... over a silly fight.",
            "description": "To break up is to end a relationship.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The prisoners who broke ................................. of prison have been caught.",
            "description": " To break out of prison is to escape.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "down",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The sad news brought me ...........................",
            "description": "To bring somebody down is to make them unhappy.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "down",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His uncle brought him ............................ after his parents died.",
            "description": "To bring somebody up is to raise them.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My wife walked out of the room when I brought ............................... politics.",
            "description": "To bring up a topic is to start discussing it.",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "up",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I had an upset stomach and brought ............................ my lunch in the wash room.",
            "description": "To bring up food is to vomit it.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Ask him to call me ............................ when he returns.",
            "description": "To call somebody back is to return a phone call.",
            "answers": [
                "back",
                "up",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Susie called the wedding ........................ when she realized that Jack was in a relationship with another woman.",
            "description": "To call off wedding is to cancel it.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "out",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Janet called .......................... yesterday but I wasn't home.",
            "description": "To call on somebody is to visit them.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Although I ran fast, I could not catch ......................... with them.",
            "description": "To catch up with somebody is to get to the same point as they are.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "up",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She cheered ............................ when she heard that she had passed the exam.",
            "description": "Cheer up = become happier",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "up",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If everyone chips ............................ we can finish the job by evening.",
            "description": "To chip in is to help or contribute.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "in",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}